Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Campus Buildings
  - D'Agostino Hall Construction
    - D'Agostino Hall, West Third Street Building Facade, Looking South, July 1986; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6585; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 7)
    - D'Agostino Hall, West Third Street Facade, Street View, Looking South, July 1986; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6587; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 8)
    - D'Agostino Hall, Aerial, Looking West, circa 1985; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6589; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 9)
    - D'Agostino Hall, New York University Law School Dormintory Construction Project Sign, July 1986; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6591; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 10)
    - D'Agostino Hall Law Dorm Under Construction, West Third Building Facade, Aerial, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6593; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 11)
    - D'Agostino Hall, Corner of West Third and MacDougal, Looking Southeast, Aerial, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6595; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 12)
    - D'Agostino Hall, New Law Dorm Construction Site, Aerial, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6597; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 9, Item 13)
  - D'Agostino Hall Interiors
    - D'Agostino Hall, Student Housing, Studio, Desk and Bed with Door, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6600; Color Print, (Photograph), 4x6 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 1)
    - D'Agostino Hall, Student Housing, Studio, Desk and Bed, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6602; Color Print, (Photograph), 4x6 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 2)
    - Lipton Hall Auditorium, Chairs and Podium, Undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6604; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 3)
    - Conference Facility, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6606; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 4)
    - Lipton Hall viewed from the Foyer, undated; UA_PHOTO_001)ref6608; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 5)
    - Faculty Club viewed from the Foyer, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 6)
    - Reception Room, D'Agostino Hall, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6612; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 7)
    - The Foyer, D'Agostino Hall, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6614; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 8)
    - The Faculty Club, D'Agostino Hall, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6616; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 9)
    - The Foyer viewed from the Faculty Club, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6618; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 10)
    - D'Agostino Law Dorm, The Commons, Reception Room and Staircase, circa 1990; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6620; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 11)
    - New Library Media Center, 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6622; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 12)
    - Law Library Extension, Stacks and Study Table, November 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6624; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 13)
    - Law Library Extension, New Media Center Cubicles, November 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6626; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 14)
    - Faculty Dining Room, D'Agostino Hall, Looking North, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6628; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 15)
    - Faculty Dining Room, D'Agostino Hall, Looking Northeast, November 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6630; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 16)
    - The Foyer Fireplace, D'Agostino Hall, November 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6632; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 17)
    - Student Dining Hall, D'Agostino Hall, Aerial View, November 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6633; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 18)
    - D'Agostino Hall, Law Commons, Cafeteria, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6636; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 19)
    - D'Agostino Hall, Law Commons, Cafeteria, Looking North, November 1987; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6638; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 189, Folder 11, Item 20)
    - D'Agostino Hall, Student Commons, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6640; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches
  - Founders Monument - Gould Plaza
    - Grace Church, Spire Close-up, 17 January 1978; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6643; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6645; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Trees and Buildings in Background, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6647; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Trees and Bright Sky in Background, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6649; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Base with Inscription, 1 November 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6651; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Spire Close-up, 1 November 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6653; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Inscription Close-up, 30 November 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6655; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Base with Inscription Close-up, November 1, 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6657; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Lower Half with Buildings and Cars in Background, November 1, 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6659; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Buildings and Cars in Background, November 1, 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6661; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Founders Monument at the University Heights Campus, Buildings, Flagpole and Buildings, November 1, 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6663; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Construction of Founders Monument in Gould Plaza at Tisch Hall, May 5, 1973; UA_PHOTO_ref6665; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Founders Monument, Relocation to Gould Plaza on Washington Square Park, May 5, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6667; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 13)
    - Founders Monument Base, Relocation to Gould Plaza on Washington Square Park, May 5, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6669; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 14)
    - Founders Monument at Gould Plaza, Looking Northwest, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6671; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 15)
    - Founders Monument at Gould PLaza, Looking West, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6672; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 16)
    - Founders Monument at Gould Plaza, Looking Up with Trees in Plaza, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6674; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 17)
    - Founders Monument at Gould Plaza, Looking West with Trees, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6676; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 18)
    - Founders Monument at Gould Plaza, Close-up Gargoyle Detail, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6678; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 19)
    - Founders Monument at Gould Plaza, Close-up Detail of Gargoyles, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6680; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 20)
    - Gould Plaza, Looking South, April 13, 1982; UA_PHOTO_001_re6682; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 21)
    - Student Sitting at Gould Plaza with Founders Monument in Background, Looking West, April 1982; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6684; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 22)
    - Gould Plaza, Aerial View, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6686; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 23)
    - Gould Memorial Plaza, Tisch Hall, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6688; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 24)
    - Gould Plaza Dedication Plaque, Looking West, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref692; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x5 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 26)
    - Gould Plaza, Students Reading and Chatting, April 1982; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6694; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 27)
    - Gould Memorial Plaza and Tisch Hall, Looking South, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6690; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 25)
    - President John M. Hester and Jerry Goldman Chairman of the Students Senators Council of the University Senate, Aerial View of Founders Monument, May 21, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6697; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 26)
    - President John M. Hester and Jerry Goldman, Chairman of the Student Senators Council of the University Senate with Founders Memorial Rededication Plaque, May 21, 1973; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6699 (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 27)
    - Construction of the Founders Monument in front of Tisch Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6850; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 1, Item 28)
  - La Maison Francaise - Exterior
    - La Maison Francaise, Students Walking in Front of Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6701; Color Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - La Maison Francaise Sign, Student Standing in Front of Building, Summer Bulletin Picture, 1991; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6703; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - La Maison Francaise, 16 Washington Mews, New Sailors' Snug Harbor Property at Time of Photo, Looking South, circa 1946; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6705; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - La Maison Francaise, Looking West, April 26, 1957; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6707; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - La Maison Francaise, 16 Washington Mews, New Sailors' Snug Harbor Property at Time of Photo, Looking West, circa 1946; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6709; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - La Maison Francaise, Looking Southwest at East Side of University Place from Washington Mews, April 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6711; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - La Maison Francaise, Front Facade and Mews Entrance, January 16, 1969; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6713; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - La Maison Francase, Artists Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6715; Color Print, (Photograph), 4x5 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 8)
    - Hostess, La Maison Francaise, Mrs. Ada Mordacques Squiers, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6717; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 9)
    - La Maison Francaise, Arthur Shatz, undated; Ua_PHOTO_001_ref6719; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4x6 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 10)
    - La Maison Francaise, Doorway Entrance Close-up, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6721; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 11)
    - La Maison Francaise, Building Facade with Student Walking in Front, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6723; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 12)
    - La Maison Francaise, Washington Mews Arch and Front Facade, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6725; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 13)
    - La Maison Francaise, 2-4 1/2 University Place and 16 Washington Mews, West Side of University Place, circa 1946; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6727; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 14)
    - La Maison Francaise, Looking West with Buildings in Background, April 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6729; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 15)
    - La Maison Francaise Proposed Facade, Artists Rendering, circa 1955; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6731; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 16)
    - La Maison Francaise, Old Front Door Close-up, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6733; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 17)
    - La Maison Francaise, Old Front Door and Facade, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6735; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 3 1/2x4 1/2 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 18)
    - La Maison Francaise, Old Front Door and Facade Illuminated, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6737; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 4 1/2x 3 1/2 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 19)
    - La Maison Francaise, Old Facade, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6739; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 20)
    - La Maison Francaise, Facade and Mews Archway, Looking Southwest, April 26, 1957; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6741; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 21)
    - La Maison Francaise, View From Building Across the Street, May 12, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6743; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 22)
    - La Maison Francaise, Reading Room with French Map, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6745; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 23)
  - La Maison Francaise - Events
    - Book Signing with Tom Bishop at La Maison Francaise, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6748; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 190, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Reading of Beckett's Poetry and Prose at La Maison Francaise, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6750; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 4)
      New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University -- Buildings.; Oliva, L. Jay (Lawrence Jay), 1933-2014
    - Colloquium on Rural Life in Urban Society Today, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6752; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Mayor of Barcelona Speaking at La Maison Francaise, March 24, 1983; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6754; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Recital by Hugues Cuenod at La Maison Francaise Accompanied By David Noakes, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6756; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 5)
    - Lecture by Poet Francois Ponge at La maison Francaise, December 16, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6758; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 6)
    - Fashion Show, La Maison Francaise, October 15, 1974; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6760; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 7)
    - Lecture by Composer and Conductor Pierre Boulez, February 23, 1972; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6762; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 3, Item 8)
  - La Maison Francaise - Interiors
    - La Maison Francaise Sitting Room with Stage, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6765; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 190, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - La Maison Francaise, Staircase Close-up, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6767; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 190, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - La Maison Francaise, Chandelier, 1986; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6769; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 190, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - La Maison, Francaise, Fireplace and Mirror, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6771; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 190, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - La Maison, Francaise, Tapestry, 1960; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6773; Black and White Print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 190, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - Fraternity Houses, 3-5 Washington Place
    - Fraternity Houses, Exterior, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6776; Black and White print (photograph), 3.5 x 5 inches (Box 190, Folder 5, Item 1)
      Fraternal organizations; New York University -- Buildings.; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; Greek letter societies.; Student activities.
    - Fraternity Houses, Interior, 1979; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6778; Black and White Print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 190, Folder 5, Item 2)
      New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University -- Buildings.; Greek letter societies.; Fraternal organizations
    - Fraternity Houses, New Dorm Spaces, 1983; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6780; Black and White Print (Photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 190, Folder 5, Item 3)
      Fraternal organizations; Greek letter societies.; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University -- Buildings.
  - Galleria (Philip Johnson's Proposed Enclosure of Washington Sq. East, Model/Rendering and Presentations)
    - Galleria Proposal, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6783; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Galleria Proposal, Rendering, 1966; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6785; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 2)
      New York University -- Buildings.; Architectural drawings (visual works); New York University -- Washington Square Campus.
    - Galleria Proposal, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6787; Black and White Print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 3)
      New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University -- Buildings.; Architectural drawings (visual works)
    - Galleria Proposal, Arcade Rendering, 1968; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6789; Black and White print (Photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 4)
      New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; Architectural drawings (visual works); New York University -- Buildings.
    - Galleria Proposal, Arcade Rendering, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6791; Black and White print (Photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 5)
      Architectural drawings (visual works); New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University -- Buildings.
    - Galleria Proposal, Arcade, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6793; Black and White print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 6)
      Architectural drawings (visual works); New York University -- Buildings.; Architecture.; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.
    - Galleria, Rendering, 1966; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6795; Black and White Print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Galleria, Rendering, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6797; Black and White Print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 8)
      Architectural drawings (visual works); Architecture.; New York University -- Buildings.; New York University -- Washington Square Campus.
    - Galleria Arch, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6799; Black and White print (Photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 9)
      New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University -- Buildings.; Architectural drawings (visual works); Architecture.
    - Galleria, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6801; Black and White print (Photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 10)
      New York University -- Washington Square Campus.; New York University -- Buildings.; Acculturation |z Brazil.; Architecture.; Architectural drawings (visual works)
    - Galleria Arch, Looking East, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6805; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Galleria, Looking East, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6807; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Galleria Facade, Looking Southeast, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6808; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 13)
    - Johnson and Foster Bulding Plans for Galleria Interior, Looking West, Rendering, May 15, 1968; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6811; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 14)
    - Philip Johnson's Plan for East and Southeast Sides of Washington Square, Showing Galleria, October 10, 1966; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6813; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 15)
    - Galleria Looking Southeast, Rudolph Assocation Rendering, Feburary 1, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6803; Color Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 16)
    - Galleria Looking West, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6815; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 17)
    - Washington Square Park and Galleria, Looking South Southwest, November 12, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6817; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 18)
    - Galeria Arch, Looking Up at the Sky, Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6819; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 19)
    - George A. Murphy, Samuel D. Leiderdorf, and Dr. James M. Hester (left to right), Looking down at Galleria Plans, November 12, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6821; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 20)
    - George A. Murphy, Samuel D. Leiderdorf, and Dr. James M. Hester, Examining Galleria Plans, November 12, 1964; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6823; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 21)
    - Alternate Galleria Plan, Looking East, Rendering, August 21, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6825; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 22)
    - Galeria Plan, Looking Southeast, Artist Rendering, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6827; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 23)
    - Savini Classico Risorante Milanese, Milano Galleria, Seen by Preident Hester, Postcard, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6829; Color (Print), Postcard, 4x6 inches (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 24)
    - Galleria Arch and Facade, Proposal, Rendering, 1965; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6831; Color Print, (Photograph), 7x9 (Box 191, Folder 1, Item 25)
  - General - Maps, Zoning, Models, Shadows, Multiple Buildings, Contact Sheets, and Unidentified Buildings
    - Map of New York University Campus and Greenwich Village, Rendering, Aerial, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6834; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Chan House - Fine Arts Building, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6836; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x7 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Faculty Club 22 Washington Square North, June 4, 1969; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6838; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 8x10 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - Singer Building, 561 Broadway, undated; UA_PHOTO_001_ref6840; Black and White Print, (Photograph), 5x8 inches (Box 191, Folder 2, Item 4)